(Sheldon:)he'll kill himself.
(Raj:)Sheldon, listen to me.
(Raj:)I have a big decision to make,
and I'm scared.
(Sheldon:)Yellow. Go ahead.
(Raj:)A friend at the School
of Pharmacology
(Raj:)gave me these new pills
they're testing.
(Raj:)He says it's
the next big thing
(Raj:)for social anxiety disorder.
(Sheldon:)Fascinating.
What's in it?
(Raj:)I'm not sure.
(Raj:)Some sort of beta-blocker
attached to a molecule
(Raj:)extracted from
the urine of cows.
(Sheldon:)I like cows.
(Raj:)That's not the point.
(Sheldon:)It was its own
point. Go on.
(Raj:)I'm a scientist.
(Raj:)My ability to think
is my bread and butter.
(Raj:)I'm afraid if I take this,
I might lose
(Raj:)that special, unique something that
makes me so successful in my field.
(Sheldon:)Rajesh, I've had
the privilege
(Sheldon:)of working alongside
you for many years.
(Sheldon:)My recommendation is that you
gobble these up like Tic Tacs.
(Howard:)Okay, I'm still trying
to work this out.